{
    "id": "2c94adebccd44dccb00b391116272490",
    "title": "For, since, in and from",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "633a027adab745388bd9be20638e88e6",
            "title": "For, Since, In and From",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I once studied classical music ……………… six months.",
                    "description": "We use 'for' with a period of time. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That house has been empty …………….. six months.",
                    "description": "Use 'for' with a period of time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am going to France ……………… the summer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have known him ………………. our school days.",
                    "description": "We use since with the starting point of actions or situations. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have known him ……………… a long time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "since"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How long have you been here ………………?",
                    "description": "We use for to indicate duration.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven’t met him ………………… months.",
                    "description": "After negatives and superlatives, 'in' can be used to talk about duration.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "for",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was the worst storm ………………… decades.",
                    "description": "After negatives and superlatives, 'in' can be used to talk about duration.",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "for",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He loved music ……………….. his earliest childhood.",
                    "description": "'From' can be used with a present perfect tense in expressions that mean 'right from the start'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "since",
                        "from",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be at home ........................... morning on.",
                    "description": "Both since and from can be used to give the starting point of actions. Since is mainly used with perfect tenses. From is used in other cases.",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "since",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}